danielsburg was a hero in our family and
I remember my father when I was only six
years old explaining to me that this man
this one man had decided to tell the
American people the truth when everybody
else was lying about the truth now my
mom came from a very large family
um I have 27 first cousins on my mom's
side and many of them seven of them of
the 27 uh fought in Vietnam and thought
that they were fighting in Vietnam for
the right reasons and believed what they
were being told that we were the good
guys we were on the side of
righteousness we were there to protect
the American people and to protect the
American way of life and we were winning
and all of that was a lie and we didn't
even know it was a lie until Dan
Ellsberg told us so this was revelatory
and my parents made sure that we
understood even at those young ages at
Daniel Ellsberg was a bona fide American
Hero